{
    "subject": "resource/The_Drowsy_Chaperone",
    "predicate": "property/productions",
    "object": "2001",
    "human_readable": "The Drowsy Chaperone had its production in 2001.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.786627471446991,
            "question": "What decade was the production of The Drowsy Chaperone in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7826015949249268,
            "question": "What year did the production of The Drowsy Chaperone take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6716757416725159,
            "question": "When was The Drowsy Chaperone first produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316492557525635,
            "question": "Was The Drowsy Chaperone a success upon its debut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6022125482559204,
            "question": "Where was The Drowsy Chaperone first produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4997212588787079,
            "question": "What type of performance is The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43275126814842224,
            "question": "What is the genre of The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4221116602420807,
            "question": "Is The Drowsy Chaperone a musical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3606797456741333,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2646876573562622,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors or actresses associated with The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Drowsy Chaperone had its production in 2001.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1117_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in The Drowsy Chaperone?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1117_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Drowsy Chaperone a musical?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1117_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of The Drowsy Chaperone?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1117_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_169.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1117_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the production of The Drowsy Chaperone, but it does not include a specific mention of it having its production in 2001. It is mentioned that The Drowsy Chaperone premiered at the 1999 Toronto Fringe Theatre Festival and then was produced at Toronto's Winter Garden Theatre in 2001, but the primary focus of this statement seems to be on the 2001 production being part of a larger run, rather than marking its first production."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, \u201cThe Drowsy Chaperone\u201d was produced at Toronto\u2019s Winter Garden Theatre in 2001. Therefore, the statement that \u201cThe Drowsy Chaperone had its production in 2001\u201d is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that \"For The Record: ...  The current creative team and cast comes directly from a run (Nov 18, 2005 thru Dec 24, 2005) at the Ahmanson in Los Angeles, CA under the auspices of Center Theatre Group.\" However, this contradicts the claim of a production in 2001.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}